Rajesh M

Full Stack Developer - MERN

m.rajeshmanohar@gmail.com

+91 9791967710

477, Vattipillaiyar kovil main road, Kumbakonam-612001.

Profile

 Certified Full Stack Developer – MERN stack, completed Full Stack Developer Course in GUVI, Located at IIT-M Research Park.

Projects

Blog Web Application.

(July – Sep 2022)

User can create their own blog and they can view others blogs like Facebook and Instagram.

Live URL: https://blogapp-rajeshm.netlify.app

Quiz Web Application.

(June – Aug 2022)

Admin can create questions and let user to answer the questions on timer basis (30 sec), user can check their result once quiz ends.

Live URL: https://quizapp-rajeshm.netlify.app

React Markdown Editor and Viewer web Application. (Mar – May 2022) User can enter Markdown text in editor & View their live output simultaneously in viewer to check whether their text is correct.

Live URL: https://react-markdown-rajeshm.netlify.app

Product Rental Web Application.

(Dec 2021 – Feb 2022)

Customer can book a product for rental in hour basis and pay through Razor pay.

Live URL: https://product-rental-rajeshm.netlify.app

Certification

Full Stack Developer Course - MERN

(Nov 2021 – Till-date)

GUVI – IIT-M Research Park, Chennai

Experience

Vice-Principal (Mar 2018 – Mar 2022)

PRIST University, Thanjavur.

Graduate Engineer Trainee (Sep 2013 – Sep 2015)

Thiru Arroran Sugars Pvt., Ltd., Thirumandangudi.

Education

M-Tech, Manufacturing Technology (Mar 2016 – Mar 2018)

PRIST University, Thanjavur.

B-Tech, Mechanical Engineering (Mar 2009 – Mar 2013)

SASTRA University., Thanjavur.

Skills

React Js.

HTMI

CSS

Node Js.

Express

Mongo Db

Sql

AWS

Javascript

Redux

Bootstrap

Git Hub

Netlify

Links

Portfolio & Git Hub

Click Here To View It

LinkedIn

Click Here To View It

Netlify

Click Here To View It

Languages

English

Tamil